Guide to the Hiram Larew literary papers, 1947-2018 MS2225
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Hiram Larew literary papers
1947-2019
1967-2019
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Larew, Hiram
MS2225
15 Linear Feet
This collection contains correspondence, contact lists, notebooks, journals, working files, manuscripts, poems, drafts, pictures and drawings, professional journals, magazines, serials, chapbooks, promotional materials, clippings, maps, brochures, schedules, workshop presentations and plans, CD's, DVDs, cassette tapes, VHS tapes and photographs pertaining to the works and poetry career of poet Hiram Larew. The materials date from 1947-2019, with the bulk of the materials dated from 1967-2019.
Restrictions on Access
This collection is open for use.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Hiram Larew, 2007(Accession 2007.046), 2016 (Accession 2016.122), and 2019 (Accession 2019.003)
Arrangement
Organized into seven series: Correspondence and contacts, Writings and drafts, Published works, Promotional materials and events, Workshops and conferences, Audiovisual materials, Photographs.
Historical or Biographical Note
Hiram Larew (1953-) is an award winning poet based in the Washington, DC area, and an advocate for diverse voices in poetry. Born in 1953, Hiram Larew received his batchelor's degree from the University of Georgia and both a master's and PhD degrees from Oregon State University. In addition to his successful life as a poet, Larew enjoyed a distinguished career as an agricultual scientist and the Director of International Programs for the National Institute for Food and Agriculture at the U.S. Department of Agriculture before retiring in 2015.
Larew has published his poetry in many journals, books and collections and has received four Pushcart nominations and awards from Louisiana Literature, the washington review and others. His first collection of poems was published in 1999 by the City of Baltimore as the winning entry in the Artscape poetry competition. His second collection, "More Than Anything", was published in 2007 by Vrzhu Press. His third collection of poems, "Utmost", was published in 2016 by I. Giraffe Press.
He co-founded The Poet Connection, an informal advocacy effort that promotes the diversity of poetic voices in Prince George's County and is active in organizing and participating in poetry events that feature diverse voices. He has been involved in many poetry conferences and workshops including the Bread Loaf Writers' Workshop and the Catskills Poetry Conference. Mr. Larew is a member of the Folger Shakespeare Library Poetry Board. He lives in Upper Marlboro, MD.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains correspondence, contact lists, notebooks, journals, working files, manuscripts, poems, drafts, pictures and drawings, professional journals, magazines, serials, chapbooks, promotional materials, clippings, maps, brochures, schedules, workshop presentations and plans, CD's, DVDs, cassette tapes, VHS tapes, photographs and books. The materials date from 1947-2019, with the bulk of the materials dated from 1967-2019. The records document poet Hiram Larew's creative process, works and poetry career, and also include materials by and about other poets that Hiram Larew collected.
Separated Materials
Poetry books that have been separated and added to the Special Collections stacks all have a note that reads "Gift of Hiram Larew" Those can be found using the Library's online catalog.
Gay and lesbian writers; Poetry; Washington (D.C.); Poets, American; Larew, Hiram
- Correspondence and contacts, 1984-2019, undated; Series 1
  Arrangement
  Series is arranged chronologically. Undated folders are at the end of the series.
  Scope and Contents
  Materials in this series include contact lists, address books, letters, e-mails, postcards, greeting cards, submissions, contracts and other legal documents, press releases, flyers, clippings, photographs, and works by other authors and poets. The materials range in date from 1984 to 2019. This series contains professional contact lists and correspondence produced and received by Hiram Larew dealing with poetry submissions, published works, readings, awards, the editorial process, publicity and promotional efforts, and general correspondence.
  - Clippings: Calls for Works, 1984-1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Requests for Publication, 1991; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Works by Other Authors, 1991-1998; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Clippings, Dead Submissions, 1992; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Clippings, Readings, Awards, Published Works, 1993; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Active Submissions, 1993-1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Dead Submissions, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Readings, Awards, Published Works, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Active Submissions, 1995; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Clippings, Submissions, Readings, 1995; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Contacts List, 1995-1997; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Clippings, Readings, Published Works, 1996-1997; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Clippings,Invitations; Readings, Published Works, 1996-1998; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Clippings, Posters, Readings, Published Works, 1997; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Clippings, Active Submissions, 1997; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Clippings, Published Works, 1997; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Periodicals, Correspondence, 1997; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Active Submissions, 1998; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Activities, 1998; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Fliers for readings, 1998; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1998; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Journals, Clippings: Active Submissions, 1998; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Clippings: Active Submissions, 1998-1999; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Clippings: Poetry Activities, General, 1998-1999; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Clippings: Dead Submissions, 1998-2000; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Works By Other Authors, 1999-2001; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Contacts List, 1999-2001; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Clippings: Poetry Activities, 2000; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Clippings: Poetry Activities, 2000; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2001; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Submissions, 2001-2002; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Works By Other Authors, 2002-2005; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2007; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2003; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Submissions, 2003-2004; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2005; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Submissions, 2005-2006; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2008-2013; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2014-2016; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2012-2017; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2019; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Contacts Book, undated; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, undated; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Writings and drafts, 1967-2018, undated; Series 2
  Series is arranged alphabetically by title or subject.
  This series contains materials documenting the creative process of Hiram Larew's published and unpublished works. It also includes published and unpublished writings, poems and essays by other authors collected by Hiram Larew. The materials range in date from 1967 to 2018, but much of the material in this series is undated. Materials in this series include edited poems, personal journals, notebooks, drafts, galleys, printouts, school assignments, drawings, correspondence, promotional materials, essays, poems, writings.
  - Artscape, 1999; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Artscape, 1999; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Early Writings, 1968-1971; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Edited Works, undated; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - More Than Anything, 2006-2007; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - More Than Anything, undated; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - More Than Anything, undated; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - More Than Anything: (Notes Grace Cavalieri), undated; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Notepad: Poetry Progression, undated; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Personal Journal, works in progress, 1971-1975; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Personal Journal, works in progress, 1980; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Personal Notebook; works in progress, 1967-1969; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Personal Notebooks, 2012-2015; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Personal Notebook; works in progress, undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Personal Notebooks; works in progress, undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Personal Notebooks; works in progress, undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Personal Notebooks; works in progress, undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Personal Notebooks; works in progress, undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Personal Notebooks; works in progress, undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Poetry drafts, Circa 2000-2005; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Poetry writings, Circa 2000-2018; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - [Poetry], Circa 1990s-2000s; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - [Poetry], Circa 1990s-2000s; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - [Poetry], Circa 1990s-2000s; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - [Poetry], Circa 1990s-2000s; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - [Poetry], Circa 1990s-2000s; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - [Poetry], Circa 1990s-2000s; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - [Poetry], Circa 1990s-2000s; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - [Poetry], Circa 1990s-2000s; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Poetry titles A-F, Circa 1990s-2000s; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Poetry titles G-J, Circa 1990s-2000s; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Poetry titles K-Q, Circa 1990s-2000s; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Poetry titles R-Z, Circa 1990s-2000s; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Poetry calls/submissions, Circa 2014; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Poetry, 2015-2016; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Utmost, 2007-2016; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Works By Other Authors, 1992-2014; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Works By Other Authors, 2017-2018; MS2225 Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Writing notebook, 2008 -2009; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Writing notebook, 2008-2018; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Writings, undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Unclear Author, undated; MS2225 Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Published works, 1976-2019; Series 3
  Series is arranged chronologically.
  This series contains poems written by Hiram Larew and published in journals, anthologies, newspapers, magazines, and newsletters. It also includes a booklet of poems created for the Martin Luther King Memorial Celebration event of January 15, 2000, and distributed to all event attendees. The materials range in date from 1976 to 2019. Materials in this series include professional journals, magazines, anthologies, newspapers, newsletters, and booklets.
  - Published Works, 1976-1982; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Published Works, 1989; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Published Works, 1992; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Published Works, 1992; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Published Works, 1992; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Published Works, 1993; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Published Works, 1993-1994; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Published Works, 1994-1995; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Published Works, 1995; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Published Works, 1996; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Published Works, 1996; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Published Works, 1996-1997; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Published Works, 1997; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Published Works, 1997; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Published Works, 1998 January-May; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Published Works, 1998 July- November; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Published Works, 1998; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Published Works, 1998; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Published Works, 1999 January-April; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Published Works, 1999 May-November; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Published Works, 1999; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Published Works, 1999; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Published Works, 1999-2000; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Martin Luther King Memorial Celebration, 2000 January 15; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Published Works, 2000; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Published Works, 2000; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Published Works, 2000; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Published Works, 2001; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Published Works, 2001; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Published Works, 2002; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Published Works, 2002-2003; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Published Works, 2003; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Published Works, 2003; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Published Works, 2004; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Published Works, 2004; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Published Works, 2006; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Published Works, 2007; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Published Works, 2008; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Published Works, 2009; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Published Works, 2010; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Published Works, 2011; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Published Works, 2011; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Published Works, 2012; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Published Works, 2013; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Published Works, 2013; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Published Works, 2014; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Published Works, 2015; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Published Works, 2016; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Published Works, 2017; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Published works, 2017-2018; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Published Works, 2018; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Published Works, 2019; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Published Works, 2019; MS2225 Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Published works, 1996, 2017-2018; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Promotional materials and events, 1986-2019, undated; Series 4
  Series is arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains promotional materials, correspondence, and planning materials for poetry readings and other events that Hiram Larew participated in to publicize his work or that he organized, and for personal publicity. Also included are promotional materials of readings, events, and personal publicity featuring other poets that Hiram Larew collected and/or attended. The materials range in date from 1986 to 2019. Materials in this series include correspondence, planning documents, flyers, press releases, program booklets, brochures, news clippings, articles, personal calendars, postcards, newsletters, maps, and photographs.
  - Annmarie Sculpture Garden, 2016 March 20; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Articles On Poets, 1993-2012; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Arts Club of Washington, 2005 March 16; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Baltimore, 1996-1997; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Bridgewater International Poetry Festival, 2019; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Baltimore Book Festival, 2001; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo, NY, 2001-2003; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Davies Concerts-Poetry, 2010 August 22; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Davies Poetry Event, 2005 February 19; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Davies Poetry Event, 2006 October 8; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Davies Poetry Event, 2007 April 29; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Davies Poetry Event, 2010 May 23; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Davies Poets, 2007-2012; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Davies annual poetry and music service, 2017 May 14; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Dogstar Poetry Series, 2015 December 10; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Echoes, 2006-2007; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Evening in the Stacks Poster, 2003; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 32, Item 4)
  - Events [1/2], 2012-2018; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Events [2/2], 2012-2018; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Folger Event, 2004; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Folger Event, 2005 June 8; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Folger Event, 2007; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Folger Event, 2007 April 14; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Folger Event, 2015-2019; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Fringe Festival - Philadelphia, PA, 2001; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - George Washington University Poetry Reading, 1993-1994; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Kensington Book Festival, 2017 April; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Leslie-Lohman Event, 1997; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Miller Cabin [Larew hosted], 2017 July 02; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - New York City, 1997-2001; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Pan and Pen a fusion of new music + verse, 2017 September 29; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Parkmont Poetry Festival, 2016 April 30; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Personal Calendars, 2003-2013; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Personal Calendars, 2015-2019; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Philadelphia, PA and Delaware, 1997-1998; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Pittsburg, PA, 2008; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - The Poetry and Jazz Experience, 2004; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Poetry By The Fireside, 2007 January 27; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Poetry Poster Project, 2017; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Poetry Poster Project, 2019; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Poetry Reading and Book Launch Poster, undated; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 32, Item 3)
  - Prince George's County Book Fest, 1997 September 20; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Prince George's County Poet Laureate legislation, 2018; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 1986-1999; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 1990-1999 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 1991; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Materials and Events [1/2], 1992; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Materials and Events [2/2], 1992; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 1996; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 1997-1998; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 1999-2001; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2000; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2001; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2002-2005; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2003-2005; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2006; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2007; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2008; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2009; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2010; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2011; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2012; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2013; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2014; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2015; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2016; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, 2016-2019; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Promotional materials and events, 2017-2018; Series 4 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Promotional Materials and Events, undated; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Promotional Photographs, 1998; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Reading, PA - Berks Bards, 2015 April 8; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - San Francisco, CA, 1999; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Spectrum Gallery Event, 1997-1998; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - A Splendid Wake 4, 2016 April 28; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - St. Mary's Festival of Poets and Poetry, 1993; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - St. Mary's Literary Festival, 1995; MS2225 Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Strengthening our communities through poetry and paintings, 2017 May 13; Series 4 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Woodrow Wilson Visiting Fellow Poster, 2019; MS2225 Series 1 (Box 32, Item 2)
- Workshops and conferences, 2001-2019; Series 5
  This series contains materials related to workshops and conferences that Hiram Larew attended as a participant, lecturer, or speaker. The materials range in date from 2001 to 2019. Materials in this series include correspondence, brochures, handouts, schedules, planning, presentation, and preparation documents, speeches, edited and annotated poems and other writings in progress.
  - Anointed Pens, 2018 April 20; Series 5 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Bread Loaf Writers' Conference, 2001; Series 5 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Birthright: Born to poetry a collection of Montana Indian poetry, 2013; Series 5 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Bridgewater International Poetry Festival, 2017 January 12-15; Series 5 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Catskills Poetry Workshop, 2001; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Catskill Poetry Workshop, 2001; MS2225 Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Connecticut River Poetry Conference - Chester, CT, 2015; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Connecticut River Poetry Conference - Chester, CT, 2016; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Connecticut River Poetry Conference - Chester, CT, 2016; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Connecticut River Poetry Conference - Chester, CT, 2016; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut River Poetry Conference -- Chester, CT, 2017 July 15-20; Series 5 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Pagoda Workshop: Poetry That Shouts, Poetry That Whispers - Reading, PA, 2016 May 14; Series 5 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Heinrich Boll Writer's Cottage Residency, 2018; MS2225 Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Inner Loop Residency, 2019; MS2225 Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Poetry x Hunger [1/3], 2019; MS2225 Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Poetry x Hunger [2x3], 2019; MS2225 Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Poetry x Hunger [3/3], 2019; MS2225 Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Ropewalk Winter Retreat, 2002; MS2225 Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - St. Mary's Literary Festival, 1994; MS2225 Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 3)